Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2016
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2016
Mus. Arc. 79
Haupt, Irene
4 CD-ROMs (314 digital images in tiff format)
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Contains 314 digital images of musicians who participated in the June in Buffalo 2016 at the University at Buffalo, including guest composers Hans Abrahamsen, Hanna Eimermacher, Joshua Fineberg, Josh Levine, and Chinary Ung.
All files in the collection were renamed to reflect chronological sequence. Original filenames stated in the container list are transcribed as stated on the CDs as received. Renamed files are stored in the Institutional Repository.
Administrative Information
Terms of Access
Materials can be examined by qualified researchers in the Music Library during hours of operation during which Music Librarians are present. In order to insure access, researchers are advised to contact the Music Library in advance of visits.
Acquisition Information
Purchased from Irene Haupt, 2016.
Accruals and Additions
No further accruals are expected to this collection.
Alternate Forms
The entire collection of images from June in Buffalo 2016 is available in University at Buffalo Libraries Digital Collections.
Biographical Note
Irene Haupt, a graduate of the State University of New York at Buffalo, has been documenting the Buffalo arts scene through her photography since 1976. During that time she has worked for, or with, some of the most notable institutions in Buffalo, including the Irish Classical Theatre, Studio Arena Theater, the Kavinoky Theatre, the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, the Theatre of Youth, the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, and the State University of New York at Buffalo. In addition to her specialty of theater photography, Irene Haupt has also devoted much of her career to the photography of musicians and musical events. Most notable is her documentation of the contemporary music scene in Buffalo, including coverage of the University at Buffalo's June in Buffalo festival of new music, 1982-1987, and 2000 to the present. Over the course of those years, she has created a visual record that contains images of some of the most significant composers and performers of the last quarter century. The list of names is impressive: Aaron Copland, Morton Feldman, Leo Smit, Virgil Thomson, Steve Reich, Ralph Shapey, Henry Brant, Earle Brown, Ursula Oppens, Jan Williams, Lukas Foss, Philip Glass, Otto Luening, Conlon Nancarrow, Ernst Krenek, Larry Austin, Lejaren Hiller, Elliott Carter, Milton Babbitt, John Cage, Charles Wuorinen, Jacob Druckman, and Yvar Mikhashoff, among others.
The June in Buffalo festival of contemporary music was begun at the University at Buffalo in 1975 by composer Morton Feldman. He directed the festival 1975-1978 and in 1980. The festival was dormant from 1981 through 1985. David Felder revived the festival in 1986 and has been its director since that time.
Scope and Content Note
The collection of Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2016 contains 314 digital images of participants in the festival for 2016. The list of musicians includes faculty composers David Felder, Hans Abrahamsen, Hanna Eimermacher, Joshua Fineberg, Josh Levine, and Chinary Ung. Performers include Brad Lubman, Magnus Andersson, Susan Ung, and JoAnn Falletta. Ensembles include the Arditti Quartet, Ensemble Dal Niente, Ensemble Signal, Ensemble Uusinta, Slee Sinfonietta, and the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra.
Arrangement
One series chiefly arranged chronologically.
Container List
- Student composer Timothy Roy at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3884 student composer Timothy Roy.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_001.tif)
- Student composers Timothy Roy, Brien Henderson, Young Woo Yoo, and Barry Sharp at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3885student composers.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_002.tif)
- Student composers Timothy Roy, Brien Henderson, Igor Coelho A.S. Marques, Young Woo Yoo, and Barry Sharp at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3887student composers.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_003.tif)
- Student composer Xavier Beteta at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3890student composer Xavier Beteta.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_004.tif)
- Student composers Pierce Gradone, Weijun Chen, Joungbum Lee, Peter Kramer, Brien Henderson, Luciano Leite Barbosa, Samuel Clark-McHale, Bekah Simms, Timothy Roy, Barry Sharp, Igor Coelho A.S. Marques, Xavier Beteta, and Young Woo Yoo at June in Buffalo 2016 at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3892 student Composers.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_005.tif)
- Composers Hans Abrahamsen (back left) and Hanna Eimermacher (front middle, pink pants) and student composers Pierce Gradone, Weijun Chen, Joungbum Lee, Peter Kramer, Brien Henderson, Luciano Leite Barbosa, Samuel Clark-McHale, Bekah Simms, Timothy Roy, Barry Sharp, Igor Coelho A.S. Marques, Xavier Beteta, and Young Woo Yoo, at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3895student composers and composers.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_006.tif)
- Composer Hanna Eimermacher and child at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3898composer Hanna Eimermacher and child.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_007.tif)
- Composer Hanna Eimermacher and child at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3900 composer Hana Eimermacher.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_008.tif)
- Composer Hanna Eimermacher and Marko Kassl, accordion at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3902composer Hana Eimermacher arcordion no name.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_009.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3903.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_010.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3903composer Hans Abrahamsen.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_011.tif)
- Composer David Felder speaking to student composers at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3918David Felder greeting student composers.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_012.tif)
- J.T. Rinker speaking to student composers at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3919.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_013.tif)
- Composers Josh Levine (left) and Joshua Fineberg (right) at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 black and white digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3924 copycomposer Josh Levine and Josh Fineberg.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_014.tif)
- Sound engineer Matt Sargent (left), composer David Felder (glasses), and Olivier Pasquet, electronics (right) rehearsing Felder's Netivot at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3930.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_015.tif)
- Sound engineer Matt Sargent (left), composer David Felder (glasses), and Olivier Pasquet, electronics (right) rehearsing Felder's Netivot at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3931 Matt Sargent sound engineer composer David Felder Oliver Pasquet.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_016.tif)
- Sound engineer Matt Sargent (left), composer David Felder (glasses), and Olivier Pasquet, electronics (right) rehearsing Felder's Netivot at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3933composer David Felder Oliver Pasquet Matt Sargent sound engineer.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_017.tif)
- Arditti Quartet members (Irvine Arditti, Ashot Sarkissjan, Lucas Fels, Ralf Ehlers) at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3937Arditti Quartet.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_018.tif)
- Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, Ashot Sarkissjan, Lucas Fels, Ralf Ehlers) at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3939 (2).tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_019.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman rehearsing with Ensemble Signal members Emlyn Johnson, flute, Adrián Sandí, bass clarinet, Tom Kolor, percussion, Ning Yu, piano, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, and Courtney Orlando, violin rehearsing Pierce Gradone's Apertura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3951 rehearsal SIGNAL Brad Lubmancondoctor.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_020.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and student composer Pierce Gradone talking at a rehearsal of Gradone's Apertura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3954student composer with Brad Lubman.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_021.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and student composer Pierce Gradone talking at a rehearsal of Gradone's Apertura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3956could be Pierce Gradone with Brad Lubman.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_022.tif)
- Composer Josh Levine gives a lecture at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3965composer Jopshua Levine lecture.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_023.tif)
- Composer Hanna Eimermacher with Lucas Fels, violoncello, of the Arditti Quartet at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3971composer Hanna Eimermacher.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_024.tif)
- Composer Hanna Eimermacher with Jonathan Golove, T.J. Borden, and Tom Kolor rehearsing Eimermacher's Luftpost für L at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3975rehearsal wit composer Hanna Eimermacher copy.jpg Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_025.tif)
- Composer Hanna Eimermacher with Jonathan Golove, T.J. Borden, and Tom Kolor rehearsing Eimermacher's Luftpost für L at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3975rehearsal wit composer Hanna Eimermacher.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_026.tif)
- Composer Hanna Eimermacher with Jonathan Golove, T.J. Borden, and Tom Kolor rehearsing Eimermacher's Luftpost für L at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3976 composer Hanna Eimermacher.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_027.tif)
- Composer Hanna Eimermacher with Jonathan Golove, T.J. Borden, and Tom Kolor rehearsing Eimermacher's Luftpost für L at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3977rehearsal with Hanna Eimermacher.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_028.tif)
- Percussionist Tom Kolor and composer Hanna Eimermacher rehearsing Eimermacher's Luftpost für L at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3978Tom Kolor with composer Hanna Eimermacher.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_029.tif)
- Percussionist Tom Kolor and composer Hanna Eimermacher rehearsing Eimermacher's Luftpost für L at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3979Tom Kolor and composer Hanna Eimermacher.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_030.tif)
- Composer Hanna Eimermacher with Jonathan Golove, T.J. Borden, and Tom Kolor rehearsing Eimermacher's Luftpost für L at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3980rehearsal with composer Hanna Eimermacher.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_031.tif)
- Jonathan Golove and T.J. Borden, violoncello, and Tom Kolor, percussion rehearsing Hanna Eimermacher's Luftpost für L at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3984rehearsal Jonathan Golove TJ Borden cello Tom Kolor percussion.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_032.tif)
- Jonathan Golove and T.J. Borden, violoncello, and Tom Kolor, percussion rehearsing Hanna Eimermacher's Luftpost für L at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3985 rehearsal Hanna Eimermacher .tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_033.tif)
- Jonathan Golove and T.J. Borden, violoncello, and Tom Kolor, percussion rehearsing Hanna Eimermacher's Luftpost für L at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3985 rehearsal Hanna Eimermacher.jpg Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_034.tif)
- Jonathan Golove and T.J. Borden, violoncello, and Tom Kolor, percussion rehearsing Hanna Eimermacher's Luftpost für L at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3987Hanna Eimermacher copy.jpg Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_035.tif)
- Jonathan Golove and T.J. Borden, violoncello, and Tom Kolor, percussion rehearsing Hanna Eimermacher's Luftpost für L at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3987Hanna Eimermacher.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_036.tif)
- Jonathan Golove and T.J. Borden, violoncello, and Tom Kolor, percussion rehearsing Hanna Eimermacher's Luftpost für L at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3988 Luftpost Fuer L..tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_037.tif)
- Composer Hanna Eimermacher with Jonathan Golove, T.J. Borden, and Tom Kolor rehearsing Eimermacher's Luftpost für L at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3989.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_038.tif)
- Composer Hanna Eimermacher with Jonathan Golove, T.J. Borden, and Tom Kolor rehearsing Eimermacher's Luftpost für L at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3991.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_039.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen with student composers at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_3998.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_040.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen with student composers at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4000Hans Abtahamsen master class.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_041.tif)
- Composer Hanna Eimermacher with student composers at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4001composer Hanna Eimermacher masterclass.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_042.tif)
- Composer Hanna Eimermacher with student composers at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4003masterclass with composer Hanna Eimermacher.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_043.tif)
- Student composer Joshua Hey with Zane Merritt, electric guitar rehearsing Hey's fissu|rupT\T|ear at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4004 Zane merritt, electronic guitar and student composer Joshua Hey fissulrupTTjear (2015).tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_044.tif)
- Student composer Joshua Hey with Zane Merritt, electric guitar rehearsing Hey's fissu|rupT\T|ear at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4005 Zane Merritt electronic guitar and student composer Joshua Hey.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_045.tif)
- Zane Merritt, electric guitar rehearsing Joshua Hey's fissu|rupT\T|ear at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4010 Zane Merritt electronic guitar.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_046.tif)
- Composer Josh Levine with Jade Conlee, electronics rehearsing Levine's Former selves at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4013 composer Joshua Levine.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_047.tif)
- Composer Josh Levine with Jade Conlee, electronics rehearsing Levine's Former selves at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4016.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_048.tif)
- Conductor Matthew Chamberlain with Slee Sinfonietta (Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Kristen Theriault, harp, Alyssa Roggow, viola, Courtney Orlando, violin, Caroline Sonnett, flute) rehearsing Josh Levine's Former selves at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4020rehearsal composer Joshua lEVINE sLEE sINFONIETTA.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_049.tif)
- Magnus Andersson, guitar rehearsing Josh Levine's Former selves at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4026 mAGNUS aMDERSSON .tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_050.tif)
- Tom Kolor, percussion, rehearsing Josh Levine's Former selves at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4029 Tom Kolor percussion.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_051.tif)
- Magnus Andersson, guitar, and Jade Conlee, electronics rehearsing Josh Levine's Former selves at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4032 Magnus Andersson rehearsing .tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_052.tif)
- Alyssa Roggow, viola, Jen Baker, trombone, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, and Tom Kolor, percussion rehearsing Josh Levine's Former selves at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4033 Slee Sinfonietta rehearsing .tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_053.tif)
- Composer Josh Levine with Matthew Chamberlain, conductor, and Slee Sinfonietta (Jade Conlee, electronics, Caroline Sonnett, flute, Courtney Orlando, violin, Jean Kopperud, clarinet, Jonathan Hepfer, percussion, Alyssa Roggow, viola, Jonathan Golove, violoncello) rehearsing Levine's Former Selves at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4034Slee Sinfonietta rehearsing Joshua Levine.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_054.tif)
- Magnus Andersson, guitar, Caroline Sonnett, flute, and Jean Kopperud, bass clarinet rehearsing Josh Levine's Former selves at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4040rehearsal composer Josuha Levine copy.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_055.tif)
- Partial percussion setup for Josh Levine's Four places, many more times at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4073.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_056.tif)